STEPHANIE PROVENCE

Fair Oaks, CA 916-531-0630 smprovence22@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/smprovence/ GitHub: https://github.com/smprov22/ Portfolio: https://sprovence-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A web developer with a strong affinity for design. Spent over 10 years in the film and television industry and have strong storytelling abilities and excel in making things as user friendly as possible. Strong ability to collaborate and problem solve served me well in the film industry and is also very relevant in web design and development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages/Tools: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Firebase, Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars, PHP, WordPress, Drupal, Sequelize, MySQL, Mongo, Mongoose, React, C#, Angular, RxJS, TypeScript

Design Software: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe inDesign, Adobe Premiere, Adobe After Effects.

EXPERIENCE

Camptivities - Web Programmer

Sacramento, CA

February 2021 - present

- Assist with migrating the website from MVC Knockout.JS site to Angular
- Debug and Troubleshoot site
- Style the site consistently and responsively across all pages.
- Tools used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, RxJS, TypeScript, C#, Knockout.JS

CVICS Consulting - Webmaster/Multimedia Producer

Sacramento, CA

February 2021 - present

- Make website changes for the Housing and Community Development website for the State of CA.
- Make sure the site and all documents on the site are ADA compliant
- Produce/Edit internal and external videos for the HCD Director
- Tools used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and PHP

Digital Deployment - Content Migration Analyst

Sacramento, CA

Sept 2019 - Nov 2020

- Assist the migration team in moving content from old website to a sandbox site using custom CMS
- Format content, create tables, and add links and files to pages
- Proofread all content and correct spelling and grammar errors as needed
- Tools Used: Drupal, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

Certificate - Full Stack Developer

UC Davis Coding Bootcamp - Davis. CA 2019

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Firebase, Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars, Sequelize, mySQL, Mongo, Mongoose, and React

BA in Cinema Arts California State University Monterey Bay - Seaside, CA 2007

Major in Film Studies with an Emphasis in Editing. Graduated Magna Cum Laude.